[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What does Nugent want?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "Nugent", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Not even close.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "even", "close", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nugent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What do you want?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "What I want is the Second Amendment.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "want", "is", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Do you believe that it might be in your client's best interest now if he was to turn himself in?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "it", "might", "be", "in", "your", "client", "'s", "best", "interest", "now", "if", "he", "was", "to", "turn", "himself", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, first of all, there's no warrant for him to be arrested.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "warrant", "for", "him", "to", "be", "arrested", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Would you accept that as a fact?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "accept", "that", "as", "a", "fact", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "George Zimmerman was on his way to the store, and he was allowed to legally carry a gun with him because he had a concealed weapons permit when he went to the store that night.", "answer_tokens": ["George", "Zimmerman", "was", "on", "his", "way", "to", "the", "store", ",", "and", "he", "was", "allowed", "to", "legally", "carry", "a", "gun", "with", "him", "because", "he", "had", "a", "concealed", "weapons", "permit", "when", "he", "went", "to", "the", "store", "that", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "But if he was acting as a neighborhood watch official, then you would accept as a fact that he should not have been carrying a weapon, or, indeed, using it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "he", "was", "acting", "as", "a", "neighborhood", "watch", "official", ",", "then", "you", "would", "accept", "as", "a", "fact", "that", "he", "should", "not", "have", "been", "carrying", "a", "weapon", ",", "or", ",", "indeed", ",", "using", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "The one thing we know as a fact is that George Zimmerman was attacked by Trayvon Martin.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "one", "thing", "we", "know", "as", "a", "fact", "is", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "was", "attacked", "by", "Trayvon", "Martin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Do you accept that as a fact?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "accept", "that", "as", "a", "fact", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "No, they did not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I'll accept that he was acting as a responsible citizen who happened to be the one that the newsletter for that community says, if you see something suspicious, called George Zimmerman.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "accept", "that", "he", "was", "acting", "as", "a", "responsible", "citizen", "who", "happened", "to", "be", "the", "one", "that", "the", "newsletter", "for", "that", "community", "says", ",", "if", "you", "see", "something", "suspicious", ",", "called", "George", "Zimmerman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "That is the law, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "the", "law", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You are wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "They can all go up with firearms, can they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "can", "all", "go", "up", "with", "firearms", ",", "can", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "But you can state as a fact that his nose is broken?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "can", "state", "as", "a", "fact", "that", "his", "nose", "is", "broken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "I can state as a fact that his nose is broken.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "state", "as", "a", "fact", "that", "his", "nose", "is", "broken", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "How could it be in the police report that he'd gone to buy Skittles?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "it", "be", "in", "the", "police", "report", "that", "he", "'d", "gone", "to", "buy", "Skittles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "If there are some questions about American jurisprudence or something like that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "there", "are", "some", "questions", "about", "American", "jurisprudence", "or", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I do, do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "As far as I'm aware, there is no eyewitness that has seen Trayvon Martin, an eyewitness that saw Trayvon Martin land the first blow, is there?", "question_tokens": ["As", "far", "as", "I", "'m", "aware", ",", "there", "is", "no", "eyewitness", "that", "has", "seen", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "an", "eyewitness", "that", "saw", "Trayvon", "Martin", "land", "the", "first", "blow", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Sir, I will tell you there is evidence that will come out in a court of law, that will be admissible that will show this.", "answer_tokens": ["Sir", ",", "I", "will", "tell", "you", "there", "is", "evidence", "that", "will", "come", "out", "in", "a", "court", "of", "law", ",", "that", "will", "be", "admissible", "that", "will", "show", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin", "Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "And my final question, can be both of you, do you expect George Zimmerman to be arrested imminently?", "question_tokens": ["And", "my", "final", "question", ",", "can", "be", "both", "of", "you", ",", "do", "you", "expect", "George", "Zimmerman", "to", "be", "arrested", "imminently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "In the next few days, next couple of weeks?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "next", "few", "days", ",", "next", "couple", "of", "weeks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I would say certainly not in the next few days.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "certainly", "not", "in", "the", "next", "few", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida", "Great Britain"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "But is there anyone expectation that at some stage George Zimmerman will be arrested on your side?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "there", "anyone", "expectation", "that", "at", "some", "stage", "George", "Zimmerman", "will", "be", "arrested", "on", "your", "side", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "If the grand jury hears all the evidence that we know to exist and they apply the law as it exists in Florida, not Great Britain, then he will not be arrested in the next few days or the next few weeks or ever.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "the", "grand", "jury", "hears", "all", "the", "evidence", "that", "we", "know", "to", "exist", "and", "they", "apply", "the", "law", "as", "it", "exists", "in", "Florida", ",", "not", "Great", "Britain", ",", "then", "he", "will", "not", "be", "arrested", "in", "the", "next", "few", "days", "or", "the", "next", "few", "weeks", "or", "ever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "When you listened to what they said, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "listened", "to", "what", "they", "said", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, obviously, they did not want to look at the facts that have been released by the police department, the fact that it is highly unusual that someone can kill someone in cold blood and that person not be armed and George Zimmerman has a .9 millimeter gun.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "they", "did", "not", "want", "to", "look", "at", "the", "facts", "that", "have", "been", "released", "by", "the", "police", "department", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "it", "is", "highly", "unusual", "that", "someone", "can", "kill", "someone", "in", "cold", "blood", "and", "that", "person", "not", "be", "armed", "and", "George", "Zimmerman", "has", "a", ".9", "millimeter", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Could it be that he did attack and jump on George Zimmerman?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "it", "be", "that", "he", "did", "attack", "and", "jump", "on", "George", "Zimmerman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, I don't think we can say attacked.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "can", "say", "attacked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Can you accept that that could be a possibility?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "accept", "that", "that", "could", "be", "a", "possibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Certainly that's what he wants to assert.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "that", "'s", "what", "he", "wants", "to", "assert", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Crump"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Would Trayvon Martin be given all this consideration had he been the trigger man?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "Trayvon", "Martin", "be", "given", "all", "this", "consideration", "had", "he", "been", "the", "trigger", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "ORGAN: Mr. Crump, I'm going to have to leave it there.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Mr.", "Crump", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "have", "to", "leave", "it", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What do you make of this case in its entirety?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "case", "in", "its", "entirety", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Well, first of all, thanks for going after this very tragic situation, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "thanks", "for", "going", "after", "this", "very", "tragic", "situation", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Even for someone like you, that believes in right to bear arms and guns and everything else, shouldn't he have been arrested?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "for", "someone", "like", "you", ",", "that", "believes", "in", "right", "to", "bear", "arms", "and", "guns", "and", "everything", "else", ",", "should", "n't", "he", "have", "been", "arrested", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "You saw the tape.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "saw", "the", "tape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "But do you believe that a neighborhood watch official acting in that capacity should be armed and using that firearm?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "a", "neighborhood", "watch", "official", "acting", "in", "that", "capacity", "should", "be", "armed", "and", "using", "that", "firearm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "What is your view of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Well, I think it comes down to one word, which is race.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "comes", "down", "to", "one", "word", ",", "which", "is", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What do you believe has gone fundamentally wrong with the American business model?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "believe", "has", "gone", "fundamentally", "wrong", "with", "the", "American", "business", "model", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, I think we're stuck in a box doing the same thing over and over every single day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "stuck", "in", "a", "box", "doing", "the", "same", "thing", "over", "and", "over", "every", "single", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "The premise of your book, \"The Passport to Success,\" do you believe that enough Americans take personal responsibility these days for their lives, for their careers, for their economic stability and so on?", "question_tokens": ["The", "premise", "of", "your", "book", ",", "``", "The", "Passport", "to", "Success", ",", "''", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "enough", "Americans", "take", "personal", "responsibility", "these", "days", "for", "their", "lives", ",", "for", "their", "careers", ",", "for", "their", "economic", "stability", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "''", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Well, we don't really know how to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "really", "know", "how", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]